<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<MyGame> 
	<dialog id='0' type="end"></dialog>
	<!-- dorm dialogue -->
	<!-- CPU Dailog -->
	<dialog id='1' type="normal" next="2" color="red"> 
		<line id='1'>It has come to our attention that you have insufficient credits needed to graduate. We advise that you continue your studies an attend the next</line>
		<line id='2'>available graduation. Think of this as a minor setback.</line>
		<line id='3'>Peggy Potts, Student Advising and Administration, Fake University of California</line>
		<nextdialog>5</nextdialog>
	</dialog>
	<!-- CPU Dailog After -->
	<dialog id='2' type="normal" next="2" color="green">
		<line id='1'>Basic controls are the arrow keys for movement, ENTER to continure dialogue, Q to change forms, and R to display the current objective.</line>
		<line id='2'>Changing forms allows you to hack things, try not to be seen.</line>		
		<nextdialog>0</nextdialog>
	</dialog>
	
	<!-- Intro Dialog -->
	<dialog id='3' type="normal" color="green">
		<line id='1'>Use the arrow keys to move. Press the ENTER to continue dialogue.</line>
		<nextdialog>4</nextdialog>
	</dialog>	
	<dialog id='4' type="normal" color="blue">
		<line id='1'>What is that, looks like our computer has a message there.</line> 
		<nextdialog>0</nextdialog>
	</dialog>
	
	<dialog id='5' type="normal" color="blue">
		<line id='1'>Now what?  This is a disaster, I wasn’t planning on staying here much longer. I guess I shouldn’t have spent so much time Bug Bountying.</line>
		<line id='2'>… … I know! I’ll hack the school. It shouldn’t be that hard, their systems and security are probably outdated. But I have to move fast, </line>
		<line id='3'>I can’t afford to get caught.</line> 
		<nextdialog>6</nextdialog>
	</dialog>
	<dialog id='6' type="normal" color="green">
		<line id='1'>Use Q to put your Black Hat on so you can get hacking, and switch back to your White Hat with the same key. R to display the current objective.</line>
		<nextdialog>0</nextdialog>
	</dialog>	
	<!-- Boss Dialog -->
	<dialog id='7' type="normal" next="8" color="red">
		<line id='1'>Oh hey there Digit. I just wanted to let you know that you have been doing so well these past few weeks and think you are due for a raise.</line>
		<nextdialog>0</nextdialog>
	</dialog>	
	<dialog id='8' type="normal" next="8" color="red">
		<line id='1'>Shouldn't you be getting to work now?</line>
		<nextdialog>0</nextdialog>
	</dialog>	
	<!-- receptionist dialogue -->
	<dialog id='9' type="normal" next="9" color="red">
		<line id='1'>Hey, there Digit have you talked to Al yet? (your boss)</line>
		<nextdialog>0</nextdialog>
	</dialog>
		<!-- ending question -->
	<dialog id='10' type="question" next="10" color="red">
		<line id='1'>Do you want to go to sleep?                                Yes.                      No.</line>
		<nextdialog>0</nextdialog>
	</dialog>
</MyGame>